[{"answer": "I beg your pardon. But, if I'm not too inquisitive, would you mind telling me what IS that you're drinking", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Teeth", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "To explain how sorry I am", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Who's getting emotional", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Say, what's she crying about", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Didn't they wash your strawberries this morning? Well, there ain't a whole hell of a lot that we can do about that now", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hey! Where're you goin'?", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Out where?", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Don't you suppose you could arrange that here?", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Okay. Come on, my friend. We got to go somewheres else to get a drink", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I just walked through the gate. I was only seven", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I can't see very far", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "A mother", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Why not in a long time", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Say, my friend, let's ditch these drunks and go off somewhere by ourselves. These crazy fools are liable to do anything", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Since the war, they don't care what happens", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Do you think so", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And do you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And do you", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What more important things", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What more important things", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What kind of work", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Take me dancing", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What places you got", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Recite what", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Whose poetry", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Poetry", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "My poetry", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend? Are you rich", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well, just how rich IS your mother", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Thank you, my friend. That was EVER so cool and nice.  Good night", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Good night", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Sure. Let's stay here", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " What about my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, no", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well, what do YOU hang around for", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Now, let's see. Where were we before we were so rudely interrupted", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "That's right. We were talkin' about my friend's legs. And havin' a fine time, too", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, my friend likes to be alone. He's as brittle as a breadstick. One silly crack from you and he might break up in sections", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What are we all doing in that place", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What are we all doing in that place", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Well, he's not ready to go home. What could he do if he went home? Have people cry over his hands", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I know. But why doesn't he go home", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Well, it seems", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I know. But how", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Well, don't tell me if you don't want to", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Not ever. Not in his dark glasses anyway", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "He'll have to be", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "He'll have to be", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Well, how are you going to end? How am I going to end? How is ANYONE going to end? How's your picon citron go", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "It goes fine. But doesn't ANYTHING make any difference to you", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Tell me, where were you little", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. I really didn't do it on purpose. It was on account of the picon citron. Tell me about my friend and my friend", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Why are they buried side by side", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Did he say he was going away", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Then, you've got to go to him right now", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "She's got eyes like an Assyrian Queen's got eyes", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I did SO see an Assyrian Queen", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I did SO see an Assyrian Queen", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "In the that place's green hat, that's whose green hat", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "my friend, you'd better get out of here right away before something happens to you", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Oh, I see. You wanna argue about it. If you don't clear out of here right now, you're liable to get hurt", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Say, my friend, what day is this", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Wednesday? Wednesday what", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I don't like beer", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Don't wanna leap like a tuna", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Don't wanna leap like a tuna", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Don't wanna bark like a fox", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Don't wanna bark like a fox", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "That's what I wanna do! Laugh and play", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, eh", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Yes! Vanilla", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "He's been shot", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "my friend, why didn't you say you were hurt", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Maybe my friend will forget to wind his chiming watch one day and go on sleeping. Till the end. It doesn't matter now. Without them, nothing matters. We only had each other. Comradeship was all we had left. And now that's gone, too", "docId": "Last-Flight_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "That's right. I'm alone now", "qsentId": 76}]